=Twin Fire Dawn=
=Episode 9=
Wait for me.
Wait for me to come back.
You have to wait for me.
Yunqiu.
Don't go.
I'm so cold, Yunqiu.
(Why...)
(Why were you ruthless enough
to kill my entire family,)
(and yet still unable to let me go?)
(Which one is the real you?)
The snow is falling so heavily.
I can't see you.
I can't see where you are.
Where are you?
Yunqiu.
Yunqiu, don't go.
Don't go.
ظآزJoy and pleasureظآز
ظآزCan you still see it within the night?ظآز
ظآزThe life I long for
is tangled within itظآز
ظآزForcing me to trade pain for the pastظآز
ظآزIn this worldظآز
You're still burning up.
The doctor said you
need to take your medicine on time.
I'll go prepare the medicine.
Commander.
You're hurting me.
Does it hurt?
Isn't this exactly
how you like me to hold you?
Why are you awake?
You still have a fever.
The medicine will be ready soon.
I'm not that fragile.
If you don't believe me,
see for yourself.
You haven't fully recovered yet.
You should go back first.
I'm fine now.
See?
I'm better already.
If you don't believe me,
feel for yourself.
(It really doesn't feel hot anymore.)
See?
I'm fine.
It's just that my heart heats up
whenever I look at you.
I want you.
What exactly are you trying to do?
You should go back first.
Alright.
Wasn't your fever gone just now?
Why is it back again?
Just bear with it.
It'll be ready soon.
ظآزWhat is there to seek or desire,
trapped in worldly sorrow?ظآز
ظآزEntangled through lifetimes,
drawn into chaos and schemesظآز
ظآزYour silhouetteظآز
ظآزCarved through endless hardshipظآز
ظآزLove and longing
traced through countless lifetimesظآز
ظآزFates intertwined,
right and wrong no longer clearظآز
ظآزThe world becomes a prisonظآز
ظآزEven fleeting happiness is enoughظآز
ظآزThis heart and love slowly fade awayظآز
ظآزWhat ending will this fate become?ظآز
ظآزCrossing through
the barriers of dreamsظآز
ظآزBurning away all my devotionظآز
ظآزEngraving the promises we madeظآز
ظآزIf time has been wasted for too longظآز
ظآزHow can love remain so calm?ظآز
ظآزSo called blame,
nothing more than an excuseظآز
ظآزWhere in time did my heart belong?ظآز
ظآزEven if time has given up on usظآز
ظآزI still long to hold you once againظآز
ظآزWhen love runs deep,
why fear growing old together?ظآز
ظآزLet the frost wither
the greenery beyond the windowظآز
(This jade pendant...)
ظآزLove is so strange,
the way it entangles meظآز
(Zhuang Yunqiu...)
(Could it really be you?)
ظآزHow can broken love ever go on?ظآز
ظآزHow much hope must fade into despair?ظآز
ظآزIn the blink of an eye,
everything falls apartظآز
ظآزBound by the fate we cannot escapeظآز
ظآزYou and I caught in
this tangled love and hateظآز
ظآزFragile hearts can hardly bear goodbyeظآز
ظآزHow many times
must pain cut deep before we wake?ظآز
ظآزI once gave myself
to you so completelyظآز
ظآزStill holding on to that heartظآز
ظآزOnly to suffer your fatal blowظآز
ظآزHow desperately
I long to hold you closeظآز
ظآزYet I approach you with such cautionظآز
ظآزHow could a stand in ever haveظآز
ظآزThe right to be loved by you?ظآز
ظآزIf love is nothing
more than endless schemesظآز
ظآزUsed and abandoned in the endظآز
ظآزStill I walk intoظآز
ظآزThe trap you set without regretظآز
ظآزHow desperately
I long to hold you closeظآز
ظآزYet keep it buried deep insideظآز
ظآزA stand in can never crossظآز
ظآزThe shortest distance between usظآز
ظآزIf love can
make someone lose themselvesظآز
ظآزThen let me stay by your sideظآز
ظآزA substituteظآز
ظآزNeeds no reasonظآز